clicksvenue.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy policy - Clicksvenue

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Clicksvenue collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.clicksvenue.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Clicksvenue.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways when they visit our site, including, but not limited to, registering on the site, placing an order, filling out a form and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to provide personal identification information, however, it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users by means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

### How we use collected information

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. Users’ web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

  * To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  * To improve our Site  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings and features based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 
  * To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs. 
  * To process transactions  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 
  * To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. 

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and any data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Compliance with children's online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Clicksvenue has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
www.clicksvenue.com  
info@clicksvenue.com  
Clicksvenue GmbH  
Switzerland, 8832 Wollerau Sihleggstrasse 23.  
+34556678899  

This document was last updated on January 16, 2014
